# IGOR PAPRZYCKI



#### **PHONE**

+48 504 781 817

#### **EMAIL**

igypap@gmail.om

#### **GITHUB**

#### **ADDRESS**

Jana Kazimierza 11**B**/91 01-248 Warszawa POLAND

# **Summary**

Currently looking for new opportunitie in JAVA development.

Ambitious, highly skilled professional with four years of experience in aviation indugtes process automation engineerPossess strong software skills in Java, C++, LabVIEW & PLC.

Have a depth analytical and problem-solving skills combined with passion and commitment to software engineering.

### Technical skills

#### **JAVA 8 KNOWLEDGE**

- OOP
- Design Patterns (DAO, MVC)
- Interfaces
- Collections
- Polymorphism
- Enums

#### **BASIC KNOWLEDGE**

- SpringBoot, Thymeleaf
- SQLite, MSSQL, SQLServer,
   Hibernate
- JUnit
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery
- Android (XML, ButterKnife, Activity Lifecycle)

#### **DEV TOOLS**

- Intellij IDEA
- GIT
- Maven, Gradle
- Android Studio

# **Projects**

#### **TODO List**

Android app for managing tasks, with menu, ORMLite database, RegclerView and notifications. It works in vertical and horizontal position.

#### **Pocket**

Android Pocket app for storing website links and telephone contacts. It allows to open website in a browsersend sms or call. It works in vertical and horiøntal position.

### Kwejk

SpringBoot & Thymeleaf web application to share gifs. Hibernate and MySQL technologies used to store gif data.

### Courses

JAVA Bootcamp october 2016 - MARCH 2017

AkademiaKodu.pl

Quiz

Quiz application for Android - display questions, 3 answers and show the results at the end. It works in vertical and horizontal position.

Java BootCamp programming course for Android and Spring web application development

# **Experience**

### Freelancer APRIL 2016 - OCTOBER 2016

C++/QT Developer

The project deliverable was to develop GUI application providing MODBUS communication with industrial PLC controller & Ethernetids camera.

Application main tasks: calibration parameters settings, data acquisition, image capture, data analysis & report generation.

Technologies used: Qt Framework, MODBUS TCP/IP, multithreading, OpenCV library, STL containers.

-----

# Institute of Aviation JANUARY 2013 - present

**ENGINEER** 

Aviation engines Fan Blade Out facilitydesign and commissioning. The Warsaw Institute of Aviation center can now boast of having the world's largest vacuum chambæesigned for Fan Blade detachment tests in largest urbine engines. It is 12 meters long, it has 5.5 meters in internal diameter and weighs 177 tons.

My responsibilities: Data Acquisition, sensor instrumentation & HMI systems design and commissioning. Works mainly with National Instruments hardware and LabVIEW software.

### **Education**

# Kielce University of Technology 2011 - 2012

MASTER OF SCIENCE (M. Sc), Electrical Engineering

Graduation in 5% of the best University students.

# Kielce University of Technology 2007 - 2011

FIRST DEGREE ENGINEER Electrical Engineering